(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T22:13:23.018089",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Terima Kasih!
Thank you!
Berkat kalian, kami bisa bersinar! Beribu-ribu terima kasih!
Thanks to you, we can shine! A thousand thanks!
Terima kasih udah bikin stage ini & hidup kami lebih berwarna!
Thank you for building this stage and making our lives more colorful!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank you!!
Terima Kasih Banyak!!!!!!
Thank you so much!!!!!!
Terima Kasih!! Kalian semua keren bgt!
Thank you!! You guys are all so cool!
Terima Kasih!!
Thank you!!
Makasih ya!
Thanks!
terima kasih...
Thank you...
Won’t you just forget about the past?
Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had, I’m hoping it will last
But the love we had, I'm hoping it will last.
Bersama kita t’lah lewati
Together we've passed through it all,
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes became memories.
Pastikan artinya ‘kan cerahkan mu nanti
Make sure its meaning will brighten your future.
To do what you were meant to do
For it’s time to make it true
'For it's time to make it true.
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
‘Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming,
Genggam lah yang kau cari
Hold onto what you're searching for.
Teriakkan, “La ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la, la ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la”
Shout, "La~ la~ la~ la~ la, la~ la~ la~ la~ la"
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone.
It’s time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Bersama kita t’lah lewati
Together we've passed through it all,
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes became memories.
Pastikan artinya cerahkan mu nanti
Make sure its meaning will brighten your future,
Cerahkan mu nanti
Brighten your future.
To do what you were meant to do
For it’s time to make it true
'For it's time to make it true.
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
‘Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming,
Genggam lah yang kau cari
Hold onto what you're searching for.
Teriakkan, “La ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la, la ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la”
Shout, "La~ la~ la~ la~ la, la~ la~ la~ la~ la"
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone.
So go and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I’ll be singing, “La ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la, la ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la”
I’ll be singing, "La~ la~ la~ la~ la, la~ la~ la~ la~ la"
Be who you meant to be
頑張ろう
Let's do our best.
Jangan kau takut
Don't be afraid,
Karena pada akhirnya
'Cause in the end,
Semua ‘kan baik saja
Everything will be alright.
Arahkan pandangan mu
Direct your gaze,
Tajam lurus ke depan
Sharp and straight ahead.
‘Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming,
Genggam lah yang kau cari
Hold onto what you're searching for.
Teriakkan, “La ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la, la ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la”
Shout, "La~ la~ la~ la~ la, la~ la~ la~ la~ la"
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone.
So go and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I’ll be singing, “La ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la, la ~ la ~ la ~ la ~ la”
I’ll be singing, "La~ la~ la~ la~ la, la~ la~ la~ la~ la"
Be who you meant to be
It’s time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
It’s time to show them who you are
Who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go, oh
(あぁ) you are noob
(Ah) You are noob,
もう知ってんのさ
I already know that.
入念な漁りに 15 minutes xd
Spending 15 minutes carefully looting, XD.
身を潜めて走る先に見上げる誰か銃声! scanning!
Running while hiding, look, someone! Gunfire! Scanning!
(あぁ) ロビーでスタンバイには
(Ah) I'm honestly already
(んー) 正直もう飽き飽きなのよ
bored of waiting in the lobby (Hmm).
ランクマは残酷 私には血の味ね
Ranked match is cruel, it tastes like blood to me.
フラグメント? 実に挑戦的
Fragment? Truly challenging.
medikitの山とp2020
A mountain of medkits and a P2020.
(oh) good luck? 祈る幸運なんかより 確かな実力?
(Oh) Good luck? Rather than praying for luck, do you have actual skill?
day by day 初動死 粗々
Day by day, dying in the early game.
やりたいこと全部pingを刺した
I pinged everything I wanted to do.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
You can laugh at me if you want.
前には出れないkraberが怖すぎて
I can't push forward, the Kraber is too scary.
(victory to the world's edge)
手に入れたバッジと感動はきっと かけがえはないはずよ
The badges and thrills I obtained must surely be irreplaceable.
見せてみてよ この狂地へいらっしゃって!
Try showing me, come to this madness!
oh baby
I need you, I need you so cold
忘れたリロード ついてこないランク
Forgot to reload, rank not following.
買い揃えた豪華なスキン
Luxurious skins lined up.
広大すぎる大地のうえ ここはどこ? over
Above the vast land, where am I? Over.
拾い上げた1 killが そう私を強くしていくわ
The 1 kill I picked up is what makes me stronger.
positioning! 高所から覗かれるのは癪ね
Positioning! It's annoying to be watched from high ground.
(oh) shhh! 軽快に 1.2.3.
(Oh) Shhh! Lightly, 1, 2, 3.
●ぬのは嫌で trip→trip
I don't want to get caught in a trip.
気がついたらround 3で アレレ
When I realized, round 3? Huh?
...隠れていただけ?
...Was I just hiding?
night and dayで fighting 辛々
Fighting night and day, painfully.
ラグなんじゃないのは全部わかっている
I know it's not lag.
泣いたって辞めないさ これが私のkill pointになるとも知らずにね
Even if I cry, I won't quit, without knowing this will become my kill point.
(victory to the world's edge)
共に掴み叩きたいんだ 熱き頭脳中を
I want to grab and smash that hot head together.
心地いいの この狂気に染まっちまったいて!
It feels good, I'm tainted by this madness!
b.p.m走ったって a.i.mはブレないで
Even if the B.P.M runs, the A.I.M won't shake.
day by day 潜って まだまだ
Day by day, diving, still more.
モニター越しにアイコンタクトとって
Making eye contact through the monitor.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
You can laugh at me if you want.
ただみんなにいつかチャンピオンと呼びやすだけ
I'll just make everyone call me champion someday.
(victory to the world's edge)
絶対追い抜くよ あの光るダイブ軌道を
I'll definitely overtake that shining dive trail.
忘れられないほどの勝利を願っちまって
Wishing for a victory so unforgettable.
狂地を行こう gg!
Let's go to the madness, GG!
忘れたリロード ついてこないランク
Forgot to reload, rank not following.
買い揃えた豪華なスキン
Luxurious skins lined up.
広大すぎる大地のうえ ここはどこ? over
Above the vast land, where am I? Over.
拾い上げた1 killが そう私を強くしていくわ
The 1 kill I picked up is what makes me stronger.
positioning! 高所から覗かれるのは癪ね
Positioning! It's annoying to be watched from high ground.
(oh) shhh! 軽快に 1.2.3.
(Oh) Shhh! Lightly, 1, 2, 3.
●ぬのは嫌で trip→trip
I don't want to get caught in a trip.
気がついたらround 3で アレレ
When I realized, round 3? Huh?
...隠れていただけ?
...Was I just hiding?
night and dayで fighting 辛々
Fighting night and day, painfully.
ラグなんじゃないのは全部わかっている
I know it's not lag.
泣いたって辞めないさ これが私のkill pointになるとも知らずにね
Even if I cry, I won't quit, without knowing this will become my kill point.
(victory to the world's edge)
共に掴み叩きたいんだ 熱き頭脳中を
I want to grab and smash that hot head together.
心地いいの この狂気に染まっちまったいて!
It feels good, I'm tainted by this madness!
b.p.m走ったって a.i.mはブレないで
Even if the B.P.M runs, the A.I.M won't shake.
day by day 潜って まだまだ
Day by day, diving, still more.
モニター越しにアイコンタクトとって
Making eye contact through the monitor.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
You can laugh at me if you want.
ただみんなにいつかチャンピオンと呼びやすだけ
I'll just make everyone call me champion someday.
(victory to the world's edge)
絶対追い抜くよ あの光るダイブ軌道を
I'll definitely overtake that shining dive trail.
忘れられないほどの勝利を願っちまって
Wishing for a victory so unforgettable.
狂地を行こう gg!
Let's go to the madness, GG!
忘れたリロード ついてこないランク
Forgot to reload, rank not following.
買い揃えた豪華なスキン
Luxurious skins lined up.
広大すぎる大地のうえ ここはどこ? over
Above the vast land, where am I? Over.
拾い上げた1 killが そう私を強くしていくわ
The 1 kill I picked up is what makes me stronger.
positioning! 高所から覗かれるのは癪ね
Positioning! It's annoying to be watched from high ground.
(oh) shhh! 軽快に 1.2.3.
(Oh) Shhh! Lightly, 1, 2, 3.
●ぬのは嫌で trip→trip
I don't want to get caught in a trip.
気がついたらround 3で アレレ
When I realized, round 3? Huh?
...隠れていただけ?
...Was I just hiding?
night and dayで fighting 辛々
Fighting night and day, painfully.
ラグなんじゃないのは全部わかっている
I know it's not lag.
泣いたって辞めないさ これが私のkill pointになるとも知らずにね
Even if I cry, I won't quit, without knowing this will become my kill point.
(victory to the world's edge)
共に掴み叩きたいんだ 熱き頭脳中を
I want to grab and smash that hot head together.
心地いいの この狂気に染まっちまったいて!
It feels good, I'm tainted by this madness!
b.p.m走ったって a.i.mはブレないで
Even if the B.P.M runs, the A.I.M won't shake.
day by day 潜って まだまだ
Day by day, diving, still more.
モニター越しにアイコンタクトとって
Making eye contact through the monitor.
笑ってくれたっていいさ
You can laugh at me if you want.
ただみんなにいつかチャンピオンと呼びやすだけ
I'll just make everyone call me champion someday.
(victory to the world's edge)
絶対追い抜くよ あの光るダイブ軌道を
I'll definitely overtake that shining dive trail.
忘れられないほどの勝利を願っちまって
Wishing for a victory so unforgettable.
狂地を行こう gg!
Let's go to the madness, GG!
忘れたリロード ついてこないランク
Forgot to reload, rank not following.
買い揃えた豪華なスキン
Luxurious skins lined up.
広大すぎる大地のうえ ここはどこ? over
Above the vast land, where am I? Over.
拾い上げた1 killが そう私を強くしていくわ
The 1 kill I picked up is what makes me stronger.
positioning! 高所から覗かれるのは癪ね
Positioning! It's annoying to be watched from high ground.
(oh) shhh! 軽快に 1.2.3.
(Oh) Shhh! Lightly, 1, 2, 3.
●ぬのは嫌で trip→trip
I don't want to get caught in a trip.
気がついたらround 3で アレレ
When I realized, round 3? Huh?
...隠れていただけ?
...Was I just hiding?
night and dayで fighting 辛々
Fighting night and day, painfully.
Capek di sini yang lelah dengan kehidupan
Tired of being here, exhausted with life
Atuh waktu, kalau capek enaknya gimana nih? Halo Hero!
Well, when you're tired, what's good? Hello Hero!
Dahlah saja, capslock, emangnya gak biasa?
Just give up, caps lock, isn't it usual?
Titik kalau boleh ke, cewek
Dot, if allowed to, girl
Bukannya sudah biasa, detik kalau moleh ke cewek
Isn't it already usual, every second looking at girls
Bukannya sudah biasa?
Isn't this something you're used to?
Ditikam oleh kecewa
Stabbed by disappointment,
Saat dunia tak berjalan semestinya (oh oh)
When the world doesn't go as it should (oh oh)
Mungkin sudahlah saatnya
Maybe it's time
Kau coba lepaskan saja
For you to just let go,
Tak perlu tanya mengapa lagi
There's no need to ask why anymore.
Jika memang...
If indeed...
Jawaban tak kau dapatkan
You don't get the answer,
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry, try to get through its riddle.
Relakanlah, karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end,
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think.
Dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja
Just let it go, oh just let it go,
Jalani saja, dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja
Just live through it, just let it go.
Walau kadang mati rasa, bahkan hingga tak berdaya
Even if you sometimes feel numb and helpless,
Dan usahamu terasa sia-sia
And your efforts feel in vain.
Jika memang... jawaban tak kau dapatkan
If indeed... you don't get the answer,
Jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
Don't cry, try to get through its riddle.
Relakanlah, karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end,
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think.
Lepas semua kendali, tancap gas dan berlari
Let go of all control, step on the gas and run,
Terima dan sudahi
Accept it and end it.
Jika memang... jawaban tak kau dapatkan, jangan tangisi, coba lalui teka-tekinya
If indeed... you don't get the answer, don't cry, try to get through its riddle.
Relakanlah, karena pada akhirnya
Let it go, because in the end,
Kau lebih kuat daripada yang kau kira
You are stronger than you think.
Dahlah saja, oh dahlah saja, jalani saja
Just let it go, oh just let it go, live through it.
Maa ii ka
Whatever, I guess.
Comic Frontier！こんばんは！
Comic Frontier! Good evening!
ようこそ…
Welcome...
「hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE Chromatic Future」！
to the Hololive Indonesia 5th Anniversary LIVE!
やばいやばい
This is crazy!
5周年のライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to our 5th anniversary live!
まさかもう5周年とはね！
I can't believe it's already been 5 years!
じゃあ自己紹介から始めましょうか？まずはゼータから！
Shall we start with self-introductions? Zeta, you're up!
よし…あっ後ろか。アァア！ミッションスタート！
Alright... Oh, behind me. Ahh! Mission start!
ホロライブインドネシア3期生のベスティア・ゼータです！よろしくお願いします！よろしくゼータ！
I'm Vestia Zeta from Hololive ID Gen 3! Nice to meet you!
はいはい！カエラ！毎日鍛冶をやってるホロライブインドネシア3期生の鍛冶屋！カエラ・コヴァルスキアです！よろしくお願いします！よろしくカエラ！
Yes! I'm Kaela, the blacksmith from Hololive ID Gen 3! Nice to meet you!
次こぼだ！こぼ！やっほー！ぼこぼこ～こぼ・かなえる、アットユアサービス！君の日々を照らす太陽になりましよ！えへへ！
Yaho~! Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun!
Kobokers声を上げて！
Kobokers, make some noise!
3人で…ホロライブインドネシア3期生, holoh3roでーす！
We are Hololive ID 3rd Gen, holoh3ro!
いや、NYANKA... いや、なんだっけ。まぁ、ついにホロライブID5周年ライブができるとはね！
I can't believe we're finally having a Hololive ID 5th anniversary live!
一曲目からもうめちゃめちゃかっこいいよね！その熱さ、感じてるわ！ね！
It's so cool right from the first song! We can feel your passion!
一曲目からもうめちゃカッコいいよね！その熱さ、感じてるわ！
The first song is already so cool! I can feel that intensity!
やばいっすね
It's awesome.
アドレナリン湧いてくるもんね！走りたくなっちゃうさ！
Adrenaline is pumping! I just want to run!
おいおいおいどこ行くの？
Hey, hey, hey, where are you going?
いやいやストップストップ！
No, no, stop, stop!
汗かくよ！汗！
You're gonna sweat! Sweat!
カエラはどう？
How about you, Kaela?
わあ、すごく楽しい まさか自分がここに立てるとは思わなかったよ
Wow, it's so fun. I never thought I could stand here.
でもちなみにライブはまだまだ長いから最後まで張り切っていこうね！
But by the way, the live is still long, so let's keep our energy up to the end!
張り切ろう！張り切ろう！
Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
でもさっきからライブの話してるけどみんなライブのタイトル知ってる？
But we've been talking about the live, does everyone know the title?
今回のライブは題して「Chromatic Future」！
Our concert this time is titled "Chromatic Future"!
意味わかる人？手を挙げて！
Anyone know what it means? Raise your hand!
こぼが絶対知ってるね
Kobo definitely knows.
そうっすね、一番背が高い人が説明するっす！
That's right, the tallest person will explain it!
そう来るかい！まあいいか
Coming from that angle! Well, whatever.
初めての人も聞いてね 「Chromatic Future」ってのはカラフルな未来ってことだよ！
Listen up, first-timers too! "Chromatic Future" means a colorful future!
ホロライブインドネシアはもう5周年になるからね 私たちはみんなデビューから今日まで一緒に歩ってきたわけ！
Hololive Indonesia is already turning 5 years old, and we've walked together from debut until today!
それでこれから先も、私たちがカラフルな時間と思い出を創り出せたらいいなってこと もちろんホロライブインドネシアのファンともの一緒に！
And from here on, we hope to create colorful times and memories together... of course, along with all the Hololive Indonesia fans!
そうっすよ、カエラ・コヴァルスキア！メモってね！そうそうそう
That's right, Kaela Kovalskia! Take notes! That's right, right, right.
さて、皆さんもうわかりましたよね？さっきカエラが説明したから
Now, you all understand already, right? Because Kaela explained it just now.
ってことでライブも始まってることだし 本日のライブのことをSNSに投稿する際はハッシュタグ #holoIDChromaticFuture を忘れずに付けてくださいね！
So since the concert has started, when posting about today's live on social media, don't forget to use the hashtag #holoIDChromaticFuture!
だってみんなのその…なんていうの、えっと…情熱！が見たいから！
Because we want to see everyone's... what should I call it, um... passion!
そうっす！そうっすね！
That's right! That's right!
打ち間違えないでね！いぇー！絶対投稿してね！おっけー、シェアして全部、おっけ！
Don't typo! Yay! Make sure to post! Okay, share it with everyone, okay!
でも正直言って、「インドネシアライブやるんだよ！」って言われた時びっくりした？もしもし？聞いてくれる？
But honestly, when you were told "We're doing an Indonesia live!", were you surprised? Hello? Are you listening?
そうっすね！そうっす！あたしも同感！妹のゼータに共感しているっす
That's right! That's right! I agree too! I empathize with my little sister Zeta.
おっ、姉妹！共感ね！カエラはどう？
Oh, sisterly empathy! How about you, Kaela?
私もびっくりしたよ なんかこう「え？マジで？」って感じ なんこう「え！ついにインドネシアで9人そろってライブできるんだ！」って！マジかっこいいよね！
I was also surprised. It was like, "Eh? Seriously?" Like, "Eh! We can finally have a live with all 9 of us in Indonesia!" It's so cool, right!
かっこいいっす！かっこいい！
So cool! So cool!
はい、これが初めてホロライブインドネシアの9人全員でのライブだから 実はこれはホロライブインドネシアのファンにとても重要な瞬間でもあるんだけど 世界中のみんなも見てくれるんででしょう？ やだ？答えて！はいはい！みんなありがとう！
Yes, since this is the first live with all 9 members of Hololive Indonesia, actually this is a very important moment for Hololive Indonesia fans, but everyone around the world will watch too, right? No? Answer me! Yes, yes! Thank you everyone!
でももちろんこれで終わりってわけじゃないよね？だから次はこの…世界征服するのはどう？
But of course this isn't the end, right? So next, how about... world domination?
我々はレディー！レディー！そうっすよカエラ、ゼータ！
We are ladies! Ladies! That's right, Kaela, Zeta!
この機会におけるファンの支援に加えて このライブを実現させるために支援いただいたスポンサーの皆様にも感謝を申し上ねーす！
In addition to the fans' support on this occasion, we also want to express our gratitude to all the sponsors who supported making this live happen!
ありがとう！みんなありがとうわ！サンキューサンキュー！
Thank you! Thank you everyone! Thank you, thank you!
ところでこのライブって何か違うところあるのかな？カエラ気づいた？一番気が利くから
By the way, is there anything different about this live? Did you notice, Kaela? Since you're the most perceptive.
もちろんだよ こぼは気づかないと思うけど
Of course. I don't think Kobo would notice, though.
これだよ 私たちの身体いつもとちょっと違うんだよ
This is it. Our bodies are a little different than usual.
かわいい！クルクル！可愛い可愛い！カメラこっち！こっち向けて！こっちこっち！可愛い可愛い！
Cute! Spin around! Cute, cute! Camera this way! Point it this way! This way, this way! Cute, cute!
始まったなあこれ ほらほら！こぼのかわいさを見て！これこれ、お尻
It's starting. Look, look! Look at Kobo's cuteness! This, this, my butt!
おいおいおい こぼがカメラ全部乗っ取ってるじゃん こっちにも向けてよ こぼだけは向けないで いち、に、ー、さん…はい終わり！こぼの番す！こっちにも向けてよこぼだけは向けないで
Hey, hey, hey, Kobo is taking over all the cameras! Point it this way too, don't just point it at Kobo! One, two, three... and done! It's Kobo's turn! Point it this way too, don't point it only at Kobo!
ストップストップ！やめてって！カメラ全部奪わないでよ！
Stop, stop! Cut it out! Don't hog all the cameras!
はいはい…それじゃあ やはりちょっと息切れた ライブではしゃがない！
Yes, yes... Well then. We're a bit out of breath. Don't go wild at a live!
はいはーい はいよ ゼータが怒ると怖いからね
Yes, yes! Okay, because Zeta gets scary when she's mad.
はいよ、ゼータが怒ると怖いからね
Yeah, if Zeta gets angry, it's scary.
こわいよー
It's scary!
もういいや、ゼータがカメラを独り占めしちゃダメっていうのなら…うーん、しょうがない
Fine, if I can't hog the camera from Zeta... well, whatever.
ファンのみんなと遊ぼう！
Let's play with all the fans!
さっきみんなからも大きな声をもらったわけだし今度はこぼがみんなに大きな声をだしたいっす！
Since everyone gave us loud cheers earlier, this time Kobo wants everyone to cheer loudly too!
そうっすよ、カエラの配信時間ほど長くならないから安心して
That's right, it won't be as long as Kaela's streams, so don't worry.
そう！みんなにじゃなく、みんなとね、叫ぶの！一緒に！
That's right! Not at everyone, but with everyone, let's shout together!
だってこれから歌わなきゃいけないからまず声を温存しなきゃでしょ？
Because we have to sing after this, so we need to save our voices first, right?
そうっすよ、そんなにカエラの配信時間ほど長くならないから安心して
That's right, it won't be as long as Kaela's streams, so rest assured!
まあいい、大声出していいから好きにして。みんな準備はいいかな？
Well, whatever, just shout as loud as you want. Is everyone ready?
準備が！
Ready!
もう出来てるみたいっすね！じゃあこぼから！
Looks like you're ready! Okay, Kobo first!
一緒に「BOKOBOKOBO！」って叫ぶよ！よろいくよ！
Let's all shout 'BOKOBOKOBO!' together! Ready, go!
いち、に、さん！
One, two, three!
BOKOBOKOBO！
BOKOBOKOBO!
いいねいいね！次はゼータ！
Awesome! Next is Zeta!
「ミッションスタート！」って言ったら一緒に「スタート！」って言ってわよ！準備？
When I say 'Mission Start!', you all say 'Start!' together, okay? Ready?
ああ、ミッション…スタート！
Alright, mission... start!
よしよし！さてみんな、そしてholoh3roも…
Alright, alright! Now everyone, and holoh3ro too...
「holoh3ro！」って言ったら「HU-HA！」で返してね！簡単でしょう？
When I say 'holoh3ro!', you reply with 'HU-HA!'. Easy, right?
さあさあさあさあ！準備はいい？holoh3ro！
Come on, come on! Are you ready? holoh3ro!
HU-HA！
HU-HA!
わんだわんだ！
Wonderful, wonderful!
すごいすごい！ようやく3期生は息ぴったり！
Awesome! Finally, Gen 3 is in perfect sync!
そうわ、まだまだ元気がありそうだね。だって、今日の1曲目だけでもすごく伝わってくるんだもん
Yeah, you guys still seem to have plenty of energy. After all, you could really feel it just from our first song today!
みんなって、私たちの一曲目が「100%」だなんて思ってた？
Did any of you think our first song would be '100%'?
まあ、誰もそんなの思わないよな。私もうびっくりした。ホシノヴァ気分でライブ開始だなんて！すごいよね？
No way anyone expected that. Even I was surprised. Starting the concert with a Hoshinova vibe! Amazing, right?
かっこいいっすね、しかもさっきゼータとかが歌った…いや違う、ゼータとカエラが歌った時はもう本家の「100%」みたいっす。マジかっこよすんだけどなんか、うー！ってなってき！
So cool! And when Zeta and... no wait, when Zeta and Kaela sang it, it felt just like the original '100%'. It was so cool, I was like, ugh!
あんなかっこいい歌を歌ったことがあるのかな？
Have you guys ever sung such a cool song before?
そう、かっこつけてる。本物のね、だってムーナの曲かっこいいもん
Yeah, acting cool. The real deal, because Moona's songs are just cool.
だってゼータがいつもスタイリッシュとかジェジ、ジェジ…じゃなくて、ジェイジーっぽい曲ばっかだしよ。だからさっき「100%」を歌った時めっちゃ雰囲気が違う。しかもカエラのラップも！とにかくかっこよかった！すごくわ！
Because Zeta always sings stylish, Jay-Z-ish songs. So when we sang '100%' earlier, the vibe was totally different. And Kaela's rap too! It was so cool! Amazing!
かっこよかったね！でも、それだけじゃないよ！次の曲が「NEW zomBIE!!」でした！
It was so cool! But that's not all! The next song was 'NEW zomBIE!!'!
これだれの曲かわかるよね？
You all know whose song this is, right?
もちろんだよ、うちの先輩だ、先輩だ！
Of course, our senior, our senior!
さっきもあれさ…holoroのパフォーマンスめちゃかっこよかったよ、まるでゲームの中にいるみたいだった
And earlier... holoro's performance was so cool, it felt like being inside a game.
そうっすわ！しかもバックダンサーもいたし、かっこよかったっすね！
That's right! And there were backup dancers too, it was so cool!
他になんかあったかな？レーザーも花火も！あと…すごいギミックがたくさんあったっすね！
What else was there? Lasers and fireworks! And... there were so many amazing gimmicks!
あのバックダンサーたち、私のソロライブに雇うっす！おっと、もうソロライブの話？
Those backup dancers, I'm gonna hire them for my solo live! Whoa, already talking about a solo live?
まあ言葉も祈りってやつ。でもこのライブはまだ終わらないよ！まだまだ！
Well, words are prayers. But this concert isn't over yet! Not yet!
でも…さっき何の歌を歌ったか知ってる？
But... do you know what song we sang just before?
もちろんだよ、私の新しい曲だから。だっけ？
Of course, because it's my new song. Right?
いや、だっけ？いや、いいや。
Wait, is it? Nah, whatever.
いやいや！タイトルは「dahlah.」だよ！「dahlah.」！
No way! The title is 'dahlah.'! 'dahlah.'!
おおなるほど、「dahlah.」だったか…まあわかっとったけど。「dahlah.」だったか、先に言ってよ！
Oh I see, it was 'dahlah.'... well I knew that. It was 'dahlah.', tell me earlier!
だっていつもそれ言ってるじゃん、本当にまあいいやって思っててそれ言って帰ると思ってた
Because you always say that, I honestly thought 'whatever' and figured you'd just say that and leave.
いやいや、かわいそうだから。じゃあ「dahlah.」ってどういう意味？
No way, that's too sad. So what does 'dahlah.' mean?
「dahlah.」は人生って意味。人生は重いからまあいいやって言えばいいだけ、その後人生を続けようって意味。
'dahlah.' means life. Life is heavy, so you just say 'whatever' and then keep living your life, that's what it means.
そうっすね、大人になったらね、その人生の経験を…
That's right, when we grow up, we experience that kind of life...
さいわい曲はリラックスした雰囲気で聴きやすいから、ファンに挨拶しながらあちこち回れるよね？
Since the song has a relaxed and easy-going vibe, we can go around greeting fans, right?
楽しかったっすね？
Wasn't it fun?
サビのダンスもよかった！
The chorus dance was great too!
あたしも好きだったな、で、そのサビのね、や
I loved it too. And for that chorus, well...
それ、違う歌じゃない？
Isn't that a different song?
そんなんじゃないと思うけど
I don't think it's like that though.
まあ、とにかくこういうリラックスした曲で歌うのは楽しいよね
Well, anyway, it's fun singing songs like this that are so relaxed.
そうね、リラックスどう。
That's true, let's relax.
でもリラックスの話だけどまだリラックスできないんだよ！リラックス！
Speaking of relaxing, we still can't relax yet! Relax!
リラックスしちゃダメって言ったじゃん！
You said we shouldn't relax!
あまりにもリラックスしすぎ！だってまだまだライブ続くから！
You're relaxing way too much! Because the live concert is still going on!
その前にみんななんか一言ある？
Before that, does anyone have anything to say?
こっちのおしゃべりさんから！
Starting from the chatterbox over here!
三言だけ、「アイ」「ラブ」「ユー」
Just three words: 'I', 'love', 'you'.
I love you.
いいね最高！はっきり言うね！とても明確、や。
Nice, awesome! You say it clearly! Very clear, yeah.
頑張って生きていってねそれだけ、とにかく人生はまだ長いんだから
Just keep doing your best to live on, because life is still long anyway.
頑張って！
Do your best!
サランへヨ！ゴマウォヨ！
Saranghae! Gomawo!
よし、それじゃあ…まあ、いつも気楽に元気でいこう！
Alright, then... well, let's always go energetically and easily!
人生あまり真剣に考えすぎないで、気楽にね。
Don't take life too seriously, take it easy.
気楽じゃない元気はどうすか？気楽にね。
How about energy that isn't too easy-going? Take it easy.
よし、それじゃあ続きようか。おいおい、ちょっと待って！
Alright, then let's continue. Hey hey, wait a minute!
続ける前にファンのみんなと一緒に大声出してみない？
Before we continue, why don't we shout out loud together with all the fans?
そうっすね！ほら！いこう、いこう！
That's right! Look! Let's go!
よし！じゃあ…一言で「Chromatic Future」って大声出してね！
Alright! Then... shout out loud 'Chromatic Future' in one go!
「Chromatic Future」って感じ？そうそう！そんな感じ！
Like 'Chromatic Future'? Yeah, yeah! Something like that!
よし！こっちはこっち見て！あたしはこっちにするっす！みんな！
Alright! Look over here! I'll take this side, everyone!
はいはい！それじゃあこっちはセンターね、あたしはこっちにするっす！みんな！やほー！
Yes yes! Then this is the center, I'll take this side! Everyone! Yahoo!
よし！じゃあ一緒に…1、2、3！
Alright! Then together... 1, 2, 3!
「Chromatic Future」！
"Chromatic Future"!
Everything was easy, I did it all alone
So effortlessly
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold, got all problems solved
Without any setbacks, there is nothing uncontrolled
There's no way I can begin, dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta soar a little higher
Hope all turns to be the things I desire
Layaknya burung merak yang bersayapkan ku, taklukkan gelap
Like a peacock with my wings, conquering the dark
Dengan sihir angin kan kuajak semua yang terlelap tuk bangkit
With wind magic I'll invite everyone who's asleep to rise
Melawan dunia, we'll never give up
Fighting the world, we'll never give up
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain, we're stronger than that
Walking step by step, trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have, let's go
Just believe me, get it go
It'll never bring me down, just believe me, get it go
It'll never bring us down, just believe me, when my dark days turn to my royalty
And when the universe works against me, I will just let it go
If it's spicy, just sip something, let it go
I've been living carefree, there's no bitter woes in the world that could affect me
I spread my wings and let my magic unfold, not letting it shows things that I'm big at and my feelings so well within now
There is no way I can begin, dream life that I need to win
I need to feel how all these things crumble into little pieces
I know I gotta be better than ever, hope all turns to be sweeter than ever
Layaknya burung merak
Like a peacock
yang bersayapkan ku, taklukkan gelap dengan sihir angin kan kuajak semua yang terlelap
with my wings, conquering the dark, with wind magic I'll invite everyone who's asleep
semua yang terlelap 'tuk bangkit melawan dunia
Everyone asleep, rise up and fight the world!
We'll never give up
As long as we got the strength in ourselves
We could rise above the pain
(We're stronger than them)
Walking step by step, trusting my own pace
Giving me what I deserve to have
(Let's go)
Just believe me, let it go, they'll never bring me down
Just believe me, let it go, it'll never bring us down
Won't let their cruelty steal in my royalty
And when the universe works against me I will just
Let it go
Won't guess not to do this
One, two, three, let it go